JOEL FRANCO NAVALES

WEB DEVELOPER



✓ navales546@gmail.com

Cebu City

joelnavales.com



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology

University Of Sanjose-Recolletos 2014 - 2016

LANGUAGES

- English
- Cebuano
- Filipino

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with five years of experience in database administration and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with attention to detail.



Front-end Development



Website Design



Web Coding



Wireframe Creation

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer at Wardiere Inc.

October 2023-Current

- Editing, authoring, or developing Website content, as well as directing content-creation team members.
- Backup files from websites to local folders for disaster recovery.

Web Developer at Studio Shodwe

February 2015-September 2019

- Creating, constructing, or maintaining websites and software applications.
- Using scripting or writing languages, management tools, content creation tools.